Take blade and bowl to the sink
Rinse bowl and spoon
Close top
Open dishwasher
Pull tray
put bowl on dishwasher
push tray
pull tray
put the spoon on dishwasher
close dishwasher
take fork
take blade
rinse blade and fork
open dishwasher
place plates on dishwasher
place fork on dishwasher
close dishwasher
take a spatula and pan
rinse spatula and pan
take a sponge
add soap to sponge
wash the pan
rinse pan
close tap
place pan on dryer
wash knife
wash a slicing table
wash a spatula
rinse a spatula
rinse knife
place a spatula and knife on dryer
rinse slicing table
place a slicing table on dryer
dry hands
[END SUBTITLE]